[
{
  'question': 'What was Oscar the Grouch\'s original color?',
  'answers': ['Orange', 'Red', 'Yello'],
  'answer_index': 1
}, {
  question: "Which is Neil Young's only #1 hit?",
  answers: ['Keep on Rocking in the Free World', 'Old Man', 'Heart of Gold'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: "Who died abord the plane named 'American Pie'?",
  answers: ['Don McLean', 'John Denver', 'Buddy Holly'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  'question': 'Who was the third primie minister of Canada?',
  'answers': ['John Abbott', 'John Macdonald', 'John Thompson'],
  'answer_index': 1
}, {
  question: 'Which one was NOT a recurring character on Kids in the Hall?',
  answers: ['Buddy Cole', 'The Chicken Lady', 'Land Shark', 'Hecubus'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: 'Who was replaced by Geddy Lee in the band Rush?',
  answers: ['John Rutsey','Tom Cochrane','Jeff Jones'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: 'Whom of the following was not involved in the ward of 1812?',
  answers: ['General Wolfe', 'Laura Secord', 'General Brock', 'Tecumseh'],
  answer_index: 1
}, {
  question: 'Bill Barilko descended from citizens of what country?',
  answers: ['Russia', 'Belarus', 'Ukraine', 'Finland'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: 'Which historical figure lent his name to an XML parser?',
  answers: ['Herodotus', 'Astylos', 'Artemis', 'Xerces'],
  answer_index: 4
}, {
  question: 'Who was Canada\'s only female Prime Minister',
  answers: ['Shania Twain', 'Kim Campbell', 'Margaret Sinclair', ],
  answer_index: 2
}, {
  question: "The Millenium Falcon made the Kessel run in how long?",
  answers: ['8 nanoclicks', '3.7 light-seconds', '12 parsecs'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: 'Who was the only female to play in an NHL hockey game?',
  answers: ['Manon Rheaume', 'Hayley Wickenheiser', 'Kris Draper'],
  answer_index: 1
}, {
  question: 'In what year did Newfoundland become a Province of Canada?',
  answers: ['1942', '1945', '1946', '1947'],
  answer_index: 4
}, {
  question: "Who is Canada's second largest ethnic/linguistic group in 2015?",
  answers: ['Québécois', 'German', 'English','Chinese'],
  answer_index: 4
}, {
  question: "Who was really 'Deep Throat'?",
  answers: ['John Dean', 'Alexander Haig', 'Mark Felt'],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: "Who played Mr. Freeze?",
  answers: ['Arnold Schwarzenegger', 'Jean-Claude Van Damme', 'Vin Diesel', 'Michael Keaton'],
  answer_index: 1
}, {
  question: "'Salacious Crumb' is a character from what movie?",
  answers: ['Goonies', 'Star Wars', 'Battlefield Earth'],
  answer_index: 2
}, {
  question: "What is an SP in Scientology?",
  answers: ["social precom", "sound prescence", "suppressive person"],
  answer_index: 3
}, {
  question: "Much of the plutonium for the first atomic bomb was produced in what state?",
  answers: ['Tennessee', 'New Mexico', 'Nevada', 'Colorado'],
  answer_index: 1
}];
